[
    {
        "id": "playeraPoker",
        "title": "Camisa Poker",
        "marca": "UrbaNOT",
        "price": 159.00,
        "descripcion": "Camisa Poker bi color",
        "codigo": "12938",
        "category":"camisas hombre UrbaNOT top",
        "colors": {
            "color1": {
                "front": "../dataBase/pokerBeigefront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/pokerBeigeBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#000"
            },
            "color2": {
                "front": "../dataBase/pokerBlackfront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/pokerBlackBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#e8e5cf"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "playeraEstamp",
        "title": "Camisa Estamp",
        "marca": "UrbaNOT",
        "price": 179.00,
        "descripcion": "Camisa estampado negro",
        "codigo": 12923,
        "category":"camisas hombre UrbaNOT top",
        "colors": {
            "color1": {
                "front": "../dataBase/estampBlackFront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/estampBlackBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#000"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id":"playeraFlor",
        "title":"Camisa floreada",
        "marca":"UrbaNOT",
        "price":159.00,
        "descripcion":"Camisa floreada hombre",
        "codigo":"12922",
        "category":"camisas hombre UrbaNOT top",
        "colors":{
            "color1":{
                "front":"../dataBase/floresRedFront.webp",
                "back":"../dataBase/floresRedBack.webp",
                "hexa":"#9a1012"
            },
            "color2":{
                "front":"../dataBase/floresBlueFront.webp",
                "back":"../dataBase/floresBlueBack.webp",
                "hexa":"#12389A"
            },
            "color3":{
                "front":"../dataBase/floresWhiteFront.webp",
                "back":"../dataBase/floresWhiteBack.webp",
                "hexa":"#fff"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "top Estamp",
        "title": "Top Estampado",
        "marca": "JSPenny",
        "price": 210.00,
        "descripcion": "Top estampado de colores",
        "codigo": "45234",
        "category":"mujer JSPenny top",
        "colors": {
            "color1": {
                "front": "../dataBase/topBlackFront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/topBlackBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#000"
            },
            "color2": {
                "front": "../dataBase/topBlueFront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/topBlueBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#042F85"
            }
        }
    },
    {
        "id": "jeans",
        "title": "Jeans",
        "marca": "JSPenny",
        "price": 300.00,
        "descripcion": "Jeans Mujer",
        "codigo": "45246",
        "category":"mujer JSPenny bottom",
        "colors": {
            "color1": {
                "front": "../dataBase/jeansBlueFront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/jeansBlueBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#042F85"
            },
            "color2": {
                "front": "../dataBase/jeansBlackFront.webp",
                "back": "../dataBase/jeansBlackBack.webp",
                "hexa": "#000"
            }
        }
    }
]